我刚拿到教师评鉴表
l just got my teacher evaluations.
你们听这个学生写的
Check out this one student wrote.
"我爱盖勒博士的课  令人大呼过瘾"
"l loved Dr. Geller's class. Mind- blowing lectures.
"盖勒博士  您绝对是
"Dr. Geller. You are definitely
古生物学系的头号猛男"
the hottie of the Paleontology Department. "
古生物学系的猛男  做成月历"一定热销"
"Hotties of Paleontology. " There's a big- selling calendar.
那是谁写的
Who wrote it?
我也想知道  但评鉴表是匿名的
I wish I knew. But the evaluations are all anonymous.
-期末考考卷还在吗  -在啊
- You have their final exams? - Yeah.
对比评鉴表跟考卷中
You could just match the evaluation to the exam
每个人的笔迹
with the same handwriting.
就能知道仰慕者是谁了
And, boom, there's your admirer.
只要一和女色有关  他就成了大天才
A hot girl's at stake and all in a suddent he's Rain Man.
慢着  慢着
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
为何就能确定是个女生呢
Why are we so sure that this is a girl?
肯定是女生
lt's a girl!
但是无所谓了  好吧
But it wouldn't matter, okay?
因为我是老师  她是学生
Because l'm a teacher. She's a student.
-触犯校规吗  -没有  但是会有争议
- Is that against the rules? - No, but it's frowned upon.
而且年龄差那么多
Beisdes there's a big age difference.
好吧  你这样想  等你90岁的时候
Well think of it like this, when you’re 90…
我知道  我90岁她就80岁
I know when I’m 90 she’ll be like 80
那时候看起来没太大的区别了
and it won’t seem like such a big difference.
不  我不是要说这个
No, that’s not what I was going to say at all.
我是说等你90岁
what I was going to say is when you’re 90,
你还能拥有
you’ll still have the memory
跟20岁小妹妹恋爱的回忆
of what it was like to be with a 20-year-old.
钱德勒
Hey, Chandler.
还记得你那个后来当当上导演的
Y’know that girl you went to college with
大学同学吗
who-who became a movie director?
知道  戴娜·基史东  我们一起上动作班
Oh yeah, Dana Keystone. She was in my movement class.
什么是动作班
What's a movement class?
是钱德勒修哑剧课的好听说法
It’s Chandler’s way of pretending he didn’t take mime.
听着  她要导阿尔·帕西诺的新片
Oh well listen, anyway she’s directing the new Al Pacino movie.
你得帮我争取试镜
You gotta get me an audition.
我不敢打包票  我们10年没联络了
Oh, I don’t know man. I haven’t talked to her in like ten years.
求求你  钱德勒
No-no-no, please-please Chandler
就当我欠你的
I-I-I would owe you so much!
你本来就欠我
You do owe me so much.
-你欠我三千四百美元  -喂  伙计
- You owe me three thousand, four hundred... - Hey, hey, dude.
你干嘛转移话题
Why you changing the subject? What?
-你到底打不打电话  -好吧  我试试看
- Why? Will you make the call or what? - Okay, l'll try.
好的  谢了  你最好了
All right! Thanks! You’re the best!
听着  试镜是星期四截止
Now listen, the last day of auditions is Thursday. Okay?
所以我得在星期四前弄到机会  知道吗
So I gotta get in there by Thursday. Okay?
记得星期四就对了  你能记得吗
Just remember Thursday. Thursday. Can you remember Thursday?
当然  星期二吗
Yeah, so Tuesday?
是星期四
Thursday!
你如果记不住  就这样记
Look if you need help remembering, just think of like this,
第三天
the third day, all right?
星期一  一天  星期二  二天
Monday, one day. Tuesday, two day.
星期三  哪一天
Wednesday.... When day, what day?
然后星期四
Thursday!
第三天  好吗
The third day, okay?
-谢谢你  -不客气
- Thank you. - Okay.
莫妮卡
Hey Mon?
我要听我的语音信箱
l'm gonna check my messages.
你在厕所里想到这事情啊
You thought of that in there?
生理反应嘛  她想知道还有谁也一样
Sure, you know. Nature called. She wants to see who else did.
喂
Hello?
瑞秋
Rachel.
我们家有人  快打电话报警
Someone's in our apartment. Call the cops!
你在用电话
You're on the phone!
-天啊  -什么
- Oh, my God! - What?
天啊  谢谢你
Oh, my God! Thank you!
是消防局  我们的公寓着火了
There was a fire at our apartment. There was a fire at our place.
天啊  有多严重
Oh, my God! How bad was it?
他没说  但失火总是不太妙
Well, he didn’t say, but it was a fire. l'm guessing not very good.
-快点  我们走  -快点
- Come on, we gotta go! - Yeah, come on.
你在笑后什么  有什么好笑的
What are you smiling about? What is so funny?
我要应征的角色是  消防队员
The part l want to audition for is a fireman.
这真是天意
This is so meant to be!
你这学期的成绩给得很大方喔
It looks like you were very generous with your grades this semester!
-盖勒教授  -什么事
- Professor Geller? - Yeah?
我想告诉你  我很喜欢你的课
I wanted to say how much I enjoyed your class.
谢谢你  非常感谢
Oh, thank you. Thanks very much.
不好意思  在评语里面把你叫做猛男
I’m a little embarrassed about calling you a hottie on my evaluation.
-那是你  -对
- That was you? - Yeah.
我后来觉得怪怪的
l felt a little weird about it.
你是老师  我是学生
You're a teacher. l'm a student.
但你有兴趣跟我约会吗
But would you maybe wanna go out with me sometime?
这样恐怕不太好吧
I, I don’t-I don’t think that would be the best idea.
我是想说学期结束后
Oh, because l was thinking, the semester's over.
-你就不是我的老师了  -什么时候
- You're not my teacher anymore. - What time?
其实呢  当我没说
Oh, you know what? Forget it.
你已经给我A了
l see you already gave me an A.
-了解  -开玩笑的
- Gotcha. - l'm kidding! God!
说真的  什么时候
So seriously, what time?
借过  借过  你好
Coming through. Coming through. Oh! Hello. Hi.
不对  借过
No. Right. Coming through!
好吧  还不是很糟
Okay. lt's not so bad.
灾情主要集中在卧房
Yeah, most of the damage is pretty mostly contained in the bedrooms.
老兄  这星期四可以跟你借制服吗
Hey, buddy, think l could borrow your uniform this Thursday?
-什么  -乔伊  人家在忙呢
- Excuse me? - Joey! He's working.
你穿一定很帅
You would look good in that.
灾情如何
Oh, how bad is it?
很惨  非常惨
Oh, it’s bad. It’s really bad.
只有一把我根本不记得有买过的
The only thing that isn't burned is an ax,
斧头没被烧坏
which l do not remember buying.
-你的房间呢  瑞秋  -东西都烧光了
- How's your room, Rach? - Everything's ruined.
床铺  衣服  看看我最喜欢的蓝毛衣
My bed, my clothes. Look at my favorite sweater.
那不是我的吗
lsn't that mine?
好  我对你的损失深感遗撼
Fine. l'm sorry for your loss.
这里暂时不能住人了
So, you won't be able to live here for a while.
你们有地方去吗
You ladies have a place to stay?
好  你给我听着
Okay, look, pal...
我现在没心情被搭讪
...l am not in the mood to be hit on right now.
不过要是你给我电话  我改天会打给你
But if you give me your number, l'll call you some other time.
她们可以跟我们住
Yes, they can stay with us.
请问起火原因是什么呢  消防员先生
Have you figured out what started the fire Mr. Fireman?
你们有人抽烟吗
Well, do either of you smoke?
没有  不过现在来一根也好  谢谢
No. But yeah, l could use one now. Thanks.
你们有人点蜡烛烧香吗
Do you light candles, burn incense?
我常点  我很喜欢
Yes. l do all the time. l love them!
天啊  是我害的  是我的错
Oh, my God, l did it! lt's me, it's me!
我把房子给烧了  我把房子给烧了
l burned down the house! l burned down the house!
没事  菲比  别激动  没有必要怪谁
Okay, Phoebe, calm down. There's no need to place blame. Okay?
我早就警告过她了
l warned her about those candles.
天啊  再跟你联系上真是太好了
God, it's great to catch up.
真不敢相信已经过了这么久了
l can't believe how long it's been.
钱德勒  是她吗
Hey, Chandler, is that...?
-那太好了  恭喜你  -成了没
- Oh, that's great, good for you. - So, is it...?
好  我们可以见个面...
Okay. So, yeah, maybe we can get together....
你等我一下...
Can you hold on for one second please?
怎样
What?
等你打完电话  要不要叫个披萨
When you’re off the phone, do you wanna get a pizza?
我回来了
Hi, l'm back.
听起来不错  就这么决定  好  再见
Yeah, that sounds great. We'll do it then. Okay, bye.
什么时候试镜
Hey listen, so when’s-when’s my audition?
我知道是星期四  几点呢
I mean I know it’s Thursday, but what time?
我们没聊到那个
Hi. We didn't get to it.
我带她去喝咖啡时再说
l'm taking her to coffee. We'll do it then.
你要跟这个女生约会啊
So, now you're going on a date with this girl?
宝贝  这不算约会  我们十年没有联络了
Honey, it is not a date! I haven’t talked to her in ten years!
十年不联络啊  总不能一通电话过去
You can’t just call up somebody you haven’t talked to in ten years
就要人家帮忙吧
and ask them for a favor.
要讲人情世故  花点时间走个过场
There are rules, you know? You gotta put in some time.
没错  对不起
Right, l'm sorry.
你又不是去见旧情人
It’s not like you’re y’know, going out with an ex-girlfriend.
我们只约过一次会
We only went out once.
你跟她交往过啊
You dated her?!
一次也没有
Not once.
干脆我也去找个前男友
Why don't l just go out with an exboyfriend,
来帮乔伊的忙吧
you know, and do Joey a favor?
想帮乔伊的忙  就跟乔伊约会吧
You want to do Joey a favor? Maybe you go out with Joey.
真好  我朋友乔伊也在电影圈
That's great. My friend Joey's in the movie business.
你猜我那天遇见哪个同学  豪伊
You know who l ran into from school? Howie.
我的朋友叫乔伊
My friend's name is Joey.
豪伊现在貌似在当剪接师
Apparently, Howie's editing now.
他打来问能不能剪我的新片
Yeah, he calls me up and asks me if he can edit my new movie.
你能相信吗
Can you believe that?
我跟他都十年没联络了
You know, l haven't spoken to him in 10 years...
他打电话来居然是要我帮忙
...and he asks me for a favor?
我一向很讨厌那家伙
Yeah, l've always hated that Howie.
连声好都没问
No "How you doing?"
连先喝杯咖啡都没有
Man, l mean, not even a cup of coffee first.
-真大胆  -就是啊
- The nerve. - Yeah.
再来一杯吗
Refill?
事出突然  抱歉房里一团乱
This is last-minute, so l want to apologize for the mess.
没关系
Oh, who cares?
天啊  我住的时候绝对不是长这样
Oh, my God! lt sure didn't look this way when l lived here.
我知道
l know!
听着  有个问题  这里只能睡一个人
Now look, there’s only one problem though. There’s only room for one,
另一个人得去住乔伊家
so one of you will have to stay at Joey's.
既然火算是我放的
Well, since the fire was kind of my fault,
你就睡这里吧
I guess you should get to stay here.
谁也没有错  菲比  知道吗
Hey! Hey-hey, now this was no one’s fault Pheebs. Okay?
那是个意外
It was an accident.
是我的错  你应该睡这里
Well no, it was my fault so you should get the nice room.
好吧
Okay!
你是"莫妮卡旅馆"的首位贵客
So Rach! You’re the first guest at Hotel Monica!
莫妮卡旅馆
Hotel Monica!
你早餐的蛋想我怎么料理呢
you’ll just have to tell me how you like your eggs in the morning.
我打算给你端到床上
And I thought I would bring them to you, y’know, in bed.
-你吃了这么多苦  -就是啊
- You've been through so much. - l have.
这是我放披萨的地方
This right here is where l keep the pizza.
纸巾在那里
And that's where the napkin is.
-什么味道  -就是啊  什么味道...
- What's that smell? - l know! l don't....
拜托  一班这么多人呢
Oh, please, it was such a big class.
你从来没有注意过我
You never even noticed me.
什么  当然有
What? Of course l did.
你坐瞌睡鬼旁边
You sat next to "sleepy sleeperson. "
谁
Who?
我记不住全班的名字
Oh. l had trouble remembering names,
就取绰号代替
so l came up with nicknames.
像你的另一边是发臭上衣男
Like the guy on the other side of you was Smelly von Brownshirt.
没错
Oh, yeah.
-你有帮我取绰号吗  -没有
- So did you have a nickname for me? - No. No.
你有  是什么
Yes, you did. What was it?
可爱美眉
"Cutie McPretty. "
你嘴真甜
Oh, that's so sweet!
说真的  今晚真的很开心
Listen, l gotta tell you, l'm having a great time.
还记得你之前说过
Y’know how before you said it might be weird,
师生约会很奇怪
the whole student teacher thing,
其实我也有同感
And to be frank, l thought it would be too.
结果不会  一点也不会
But it's not. l mean, it's not at all.
-盖勒博士  -博特
- Dr. Geller! - Burt!
-你昨晚睡得好吗  -很好
- So did you sleep well last night? - l did.
莫妮卡还在我的枕头上放了一小片薄荷
Monica was so sweet. She left a little mint on my pillow.
你猜乔伊在我枕头上放了什么
Know what Joey left on my pillow?
口香糖
Gum.
我们找到起火原因了
Well, we’ve determined the cause of the fire.
我知道  是我的蜡烛害的
Yeah I know, it was my candle. My candle!
不是  浴室有个电器没拔掉
No, there was an appliance left on in the bathroom.
好像是卷发器
lt looks like a curling iron.
-我没在用卷发器  -有人用吧
- l don't use a curling iron. - Someone does.
别看我  我的头发是直的
Don't look at me, my hair's straight.
直的  直的  直的
Straight, straight, straight.
也可能是直发夹
It could've been a hair straightener.
这是我放披萨的地方
This is where l keep the pizza.
这是  奇怪  纸巾呢
And... Hey, where'd the napkin go?
好了  可不能让贵客眼睛疲劳
Now there you go! l wouldn't want my best guest to strain her eyes.
谢谢  莫妮卡
Thanks, Monica.
-你会烦那个味道吗  -乔伊家的怪味吗
- Does that smell bother you? - What? the smell from Joey’s?
在这里就几乎闻不太到了
No, I can hardly smell it over here.
闻得到就告诉我
Well, you let me know if you can.
我可以烤个派把味道盖过去
Because y’know I can bake a pie to cover it.
-是有点闻得到  烤个派吧  -好
- l can smell it a little, bake a pie. - Okay.
喂
Hello?
请稍等  火场调查员找你
One minute, please. It’s for you. It’s the fire inspector.
喂  对  我是菲比
Hello? Yeah, this is Phoebe.
是吗
Really?
是的  后来发现原来直发夹
Yeah, so it turns out that it wasn't the hair straightener...
不是起火点
...that started the fire.
不  是蜡烛
No, no. lt was the candles.
对  把蜡烛点着不管实在不太好
Yeah. lt's very not good leaving candles unattended.
事实上  这是消防学校最先教的事情之一
ln fact, one of the first things they teach you in fire school is...
好吧  我该挂了
...okay, well l have to go now.
我们玩得好开心  她好棒
We had such a great time! She’s-she’s incredible!
我以为年龄会造成问题
I thought the-the age difference might be a problem,
结果一点也不会
but it wasn’t. It wasn’t at all.
就她的年纪来说  伊丽莎白非常成熟
Elizabeth is very mature for her age.
有些人就是不懂
A concept lost on some people.
所以师生可以约会吗
lt's okay to date a student?
也不是  技术上讲
Well, not really. . I mean technically
没触犯校规
it’s-it’s not against the rules or anything.
但是会受争议  尤其是我们昨晚遇见的教授
But it's frowned upon, especially by the professor we saw last night:
那位"多管闲事老头"
"Judgy Von Holier- than- thou. "
罗斯  还是小心为上
Ross, you just becareful ok.
你也不想被人取绰号
You don't want to get a reputation
叫"泡学生叫兽"
as "Professor McNails-his-students. "
-我该怎么办  -罗斯  其实很简单
- Yeah. What should l do? - Well Ross, it seems pretty clear.
哪个比较重要  别人的看法还是你的感觉
What's more important? What people think or how you feel?
-你得忠于你的心  -乔伊  你说得真好
- You gotta follow your heart. - Joey, that's so sweet.
你跟戴娜谈得怎样
Hey! So how'd it go with Dana?
我星期四该不该空出时间来做某件事啊
Any reason l should leave a block of time open? Say, Thursday?
-我说不出口  -什么你说不出口
- l couldn't do it. - You couldn't do it?
我需要更多时间  我们晚上会跟她吃饭
Hey, relax I just need more time. We’re going to dinner tonight.
什么  你还要跟她出去吗
What?! You’re going out with her again!
-跟谁出去  -大学同学  戴娜·基史东
- Going out with who? - Dana Keystone, from college.
她不是...
Oh, yeah. Wasn't she...?
不  那是戴娜·卡普兰
No, that was Dana Kaplan.
-乔伊  你都不认识她  -随便啦
- Joey, you didn't even know her! - Yeah, whatever.
故事真的好棒
Great story again.
曲折离奇  错综复杂
The yarns that you weave!
其实呢  我该走了
You know, actually, l should get going.
不  不  留下来  你应该留下来
Oh, no, no, stay! Because you should stay.
我真的很受宠若惊
Oh, l am really flattered.
但是我对你没感觉
But l just.... l don't feel that way about you.
不  我不是…不是
Oh, no, no. That's not...
对不起  钱德勒  你人很好
l'm sorry, Chandler. You know, you're such a sweet guy...
我也不想伤害你
...and l don't want to hurt you.
我真想设法让你好过一点
l wish l could do something to make you feel better.
不...  真的吗
No... Really?
当然
Of course.
我真是太伤心了  我...
Well, it just hurts so bad, l....
对不起
Oh, l'm sorry.
或许你可以做一件事
Maybe there is one thing you can do.
什么事  你尽管说
What? Anything. Anything.
这事我是刚刚才想到的哦
Well, l mean, this is just off the top of my head now.
我有个朋友  一个演员朋友
But l have this friend... This actor friend.
他要是知道一定会杀了我
He would kill me if he knew that l was doing this.
但是
But...
你能不能帮个忙
...would it be possible for him
让他星期四去试镜呢
to get an audition for your movie say on Thursday?
没问题
Absolutely.
但
But...
我让你的朋友来试镜
But you-you would really feel better about me rejecting you
真的能让你好过一点吗
if your friend could audition for my movie?
这是我的心愿  再见
The heart wants what it wants. I’ll see you later.
一切还好吗
Hey! How's it going?
从五分钟前到现在还没什么变化
Well, not much has changed in the last five minutes.
其实有哦  我烤了饼干
Yes, it has. l made cookies!
不了  我还在消化你做的自制薯片呢
Oh that’s all right. I’m still full from your homemade potato chips.
但是饼干应该则烤好就趁热吃
But you should eat them now, because they're hot from the oven.
好吧
Okay.
但不是在这里  床上不能吃饼干
But not in here! Can't eat them in bed,
还记得不能掉屑屑吧
remember? No crumbies!
好  我马上出去
Oh. Okay, l'll be out in a second.
好
Okay.
-你在干什么  -门不能锁  对吧
- What are you doing? - This doesn't lock, does it?
-乔伊  对不起  -没关系  别在意
- Oh! Joey, l'm sorry. - lt's all right, don't worry about it.
但是你看  会有印子
But look! That's gonna leave a stain.
瑞秋  没关系  这是乔伊家
Rach, hey, it's fine. You're at Joey's.
-真的吗  -当然  你看
- Really? - Yeah, look.
-我从没生活得这么惬意过  -就是嘛
- l've never lived like this before. - l know.
但也别浪费了  始终是食物嘛
Well, don't waste it. l mean, it's still food.
接着要干嘛  要不要去喝酒
What do you want to do now? Want to get a drink?
我不能去
l can't.
你得念书是吧
Oh, you have some studying to do?
不是  我得先长到二十一岁
No, l have some turning 21 to do.
我以前念大学时  我们都...
You know, l remember when l was in college, we used to...
你在干什么
What are you doing?
没事  只是觉得跟你相处好舒服
Nothing, l'm so comfortable with you.
你怕被别人看见跟我在一起吗
Do you not want to be seen with me?
不  的确是  他们走了吗
What? No! Of course, of course I do! Are-are they gone?
他们还在  不过我要走了
No, they're still here. But l think l'm about to leave.
什么  等一下
What? No, no, wait, wait...
你说得对  这样太蠢了  管别人干嘛啊
You're right, this is stupid. Who cares what people think?
我们情投意合  对吧
l mean, we like each other, right?
这样并没有错
There's nothing wrong with that.
走吧
Come on.
博特  蕾蒂亚  梅尔
Burt. Lydia. Mel.
-这是伊丽莎白  -你们好
- This is Elizabeth. - Hi.
你不是有修我的大众文化课
Aren't you in my popular culture class?
没错  蕾蒂亚  伊丽莎白是学生
That's right, Lydia. Elizabeth is a student.
并且我们在交往
And we're dating.
你们可以皱眉摇头  觉得不妥
And you may frown upon that but...
但是我们不会再躲躲藏藏了
...we're not gonna hide it anymore.
你的饭碗砸定了
You are so fired.
-什么  -学校会解雇你
- What? - They’re gonna fire you!
你不能和她约会  这是违反校规的
You can’t date a student! It’s against the rules.
真的  不只是受争议而已吗
Really? lt's not just frowned upon?
我爱死住乔伊家了
l love it at Joey's!
-漂亮  -谢谢
- Nice! - Thanks.
你星期四有事吗
So you busy Thursday?
真好笑  不知你记不记得
Oh, very funny. I don’t know if you remember,
我的试镜就是星期四
My audition was supposed to be Thursday.
你帮我争取到了  来抱抱
You got me the audition? Let's hug it up!
行了行了  要是你入选你要怎么感谢我
Okay, okay! What are you gonna do to me if you get the part?
正好  我有事要找你
Listen umm, yeah okay, I need to talk to you!
我知道他们说直发夹是起火点
l know they said the hair straightener started the fire.
但我也有责任
But l think l'm partly at fault.
我没有告诉你
You see, l didn't tell you, but...
但其实我也有放新的卫生纸
...l had recently refilled the tissues.
老实说  那个太容易着火了
And so, let's face it, that's just kindling.
所以应该我来住乔伊家
So l think it's fair that l stay at Joey's.
不  不  都是我不好
No, no-no-no. Phoebe, this was my fault
-而且我在这里住得挺好  -好吧
- and besides y’know what? I’m fine here. - Okay.
-钱德勒  莫妮卡在找你  -真的吗
- Chandler, Monica's looking for you. - Really?
好像跟饼干屑有关
She said something about crumbies.
不会吧  我那么小心了
No, no, no! l was so careful.
你一定要跟我换  莫妮卡快把我逼疯了
Okay, you have to switch with me! Monica is driving me crazy!
是的  小姐们都想住乔伊家
That's right. All the ladies want to stay at Joey's.
不要  菲比  拜托  人家不想换
No! No! Phoebe, come on! I don’t want to switch!
拜托啦  我在这里可以扔湿纸巾
Please come on! l can throw wet paper towels here!
在她家你可以对着水槽吃饼干呢
No, but at Monica's, you can eat cookies over the sink.
我知道  对不起
l know. l'm sorry.
算了
All right, fine.
这个好像很好玩  乱糟糟的
This looks like so much fun. God, what a mess.
校规里真的有
Wow, it actually is in the handbook.
我不能和你约会  或是在研究室放电磁炉
l can't date you or have a hot plate in my office.
我们居然不能再见面了
l can't believe we have to stop seeing each other.
无论如何  谢谢你为我挺身而出
For what it's worth, l did appreciate you standing up for me.
我好感动
That felt really nice.
我更喜欢你了
Kind of made me like you even more.
我知道  我也很喜欢你
l know, l know. l really like you too.
但是我们不能约会
But we can't date.
校规明文禁止师生恋
lt's against the rules. lt's forbidden.
什么
What?
光听你说校规禁止
Just hearing you describe it as forbidden,
就觉得好性感
it’s really hot.
真的吗
Really?
对
Yeah.
不管有多性感  这都是不对的
Well, l don't care how hot it is, it's wrong.
-别再说了  -不  这是大错特错
- Stop it. - No, no. lt's wrong.
这样很不乖
lt's naughty.
这是
lt's...
禁忌
...taboo.
把书合起来
Shut the book.
我们也去弄个电磁炉吧
Hey. Let's also get a hot plate.
-怎样  -什么怎样
- So? - So...?
今天是星期四  试镜结果如何
lt's Thursday! How was the audition?
啥  星期一  一天  星期二  二天
lt's... Monday, one day. Tuesday, two day.
星期三  哪一天
Wednesday, what day...
惨了
Oh!